24小时
第三季  第21集
前情提要
杰克·鲍尔那怎么样了?
What's going on with Jack Bauer?
行动不太顺利
The operation wasn't completely successful.
他们抓到了桑德斯的女儿 但却暴露了
They do have Saunders' daughter, but they were unable to remain covert.
那么 桑德斯知道她在我们手上了?
So, Saunders knows we have her?
不 还没有 但反恐局说他很快就会发现
No, not yet, but CTU is estimating he will find out within the hour.
离满足他下个要求的最后期限还有15分钟
The deadline for his next demand is gonna be up here in about 15 minutes.
把我们的外国情报人员名单给他是一种叛国行为
Now, giving this guy a list of every foreign operative on our payroll is an act of treason.
我不会听从桑德斯的最后一个要求
I will not give in to Saunders' latest demand.
我们没时间了 打电话给你父亲
We have run out of time. We need you to call your father.
说什么?
And tell him what?
随便 只要别让他挂断就行了
Anything. We just want you to keep him on the line.
-简?  -嘿 爸爸
-Jane?  -Hi, Dad.
怎么了?
What's wrong?
我让你遇到紧急情况才打这个电话的
I told you only to use this number in an emergency.
有人在监听
Someone is monitoring the call.
她在他们手上
They've got her.
你旁边有人叫杰克·鲍尔的人 是吗?
There's a man named Jack Bauer with you, isn't there?
让他听电话
Hand the phone to him.
你知道我有多少病毒 也知道我的本事
You know how many vials I have, and what I am capable of.
你也知道我的本事
You know what I am capable of, too.
斯蒂芬 桑德斯
Stephen Saunders.
我是杰克·鲍尔
This is Jack Bauer.
你已经被包围了
You are completely surrounded.
总统拒绝你提出的任何要求
The President is refusing to capitulate to any further demands.
你想保住性命的唯一方法就是
The only way you are getting out of this thing alive is.
把手放到脑后 从前门走出来
coming through the front door with your hands on your head.
那可不见得 杰克
That's not exactly true, Jack.
首先祝贺你的妻子没有感染病毒
I'd like to offer you congratulations on your wife eluding infection from the virus.
你怎么知道我妻子的事?
How do you know about my wife?
我不知道他们会怎么对她 托尼
I don't know exactly what they are doing to her, Tony.
但我叫他们别把她废了 我还要还给你呢
But I did instruct them to leave her barely functional so that we can return her to you.
东北方向出口有5个特工
There are 5 agents watching the northeast exit of this building.
让他们到前门去
Send them to the front entrance.
如果不按我说的做 米歇尔就死定了
Michelle will be dead if you don't do what I say.
我是托尼·阿尔梅达
This is Tony Almeida.
什么事?
What are we doing?
所有人到前门去
Move everyone to the front now.
上车 到前门去
Get in your car, move to the front of the building.
下来 下来
Down, down.
以下事件发生于9点至10点之间
The following takes place between 9:00 am and 10:00 am.
斯蒂芬 桑德斯 最后一次警告
Stephen Saunders, this is your final warning.
快点出来
Come out of the building now.
把他熏出来
Smoke him out.
放催泪弹
Release the tear gas.
派他们上
Send them in.
所有小组行动 冲进去
Perimeter teams, move in. Move in.
好了 伙计们 上啊
All right, boys, let's go, let's go.
上
Move.
贝克
Baker.
你怎么不守住南面?
Why aren't you covering the south perimeter?
局里命令我们撤离的 说是你这里需要支援
CTU moved us off our position They said you needed us out front.
你说什么? 为什么这么做?
What are you talking about? Why would they do that?
他们说卫星显示桑德斯正在向正面的一个盲点移动
They said the SAT feed showed Saunders moving toward a blind spot in front of the building.
所有小组请回话 重复 所有小组请回话
All teams respond. I repeat, all teams respond.
有没有发现桑德斯?
Any sign of Saunders?
杰克 我们进来了 目前还没发现他
Jack, we are in. There's no sign of him yet.
谁下的命令?
Who gave you that order?
托尼
Tony.
带你的小组回到原来的位置 快
Move your team back to their marks now. Move.
-反恐局 阿尔梅达  -托尼 我是杰克
-CTU, Almeida.  -Tony, it's Jack.
贝克刚才告诉我你让他们撤离原来的位置
Baker just told me you pulled his team out of position.
是的 我根据手头的最新情报下的命令
Yeah. I was working off the information I had.
这是个假情报 你应该先和我确认一下
It was bad information. You should have cleared it with me.
我这边有个人犯了个错误 我正在调查
Somebody in my team made a mistake. I am not going to get into it now.
托尼 这是个致命的错误
Tony, that's an unacceptable mistake.
我负责现场指挥
I have tactical command in the field.
如果你管不好反恐局 最好让别人来接替
If you can't run CTU, you'd better replace yourself with someone who can.
-蔡斯 回话  -在 杰克
-Chase, check in.  -Yeah, Jack.
我们搜查了整座大楼 没发现他
We covered the entire building, he is not here.
该死
Dame it.
桑德斯好像不在那幢大楼里
Saunders doesn't seem to be in the building.
什么意思 不在? 应该在的
What do you mean, he's not in there? He's got to be in there.
他跑了 你告诉杰克 我们这里有人犯了个错误?
He's gone. What were you just telling Jack about someone in your group making a mistake?
别提了
Never mind.
亚当 你确认我们跟踪到桑德斯藏匿在那栋大楼吗?
Adam, are we sure we tracked Saunders to the right building?
当然 托尼 杰克打电话的时候 他就在那
Of course we did, Tony He was in there when Jack made that phone call.
我把图像调出来看哪里出了问题
I am pulling up imagery now to see what went wrong.
让我来
I will take care of that.
你和克萝伊 配合现场人员的行动
You stay with Chloe, cover the site teams.
阿尔梅达.
Almeida
我希望你已经清除了那些会给你带来麻烦的图像
I hope you covered your tracks and purged the incriminating satellite frames.
我照你的要求做了 我妻子呢?
I did what you wanted me to. Now where's my wife?
别着急 我做事喜欢一步步来
Not so fast. I like to do things in phases.
你现在应该知道了 刚才是第一步
You should know that by now. That was phase one.
下面谈谈我女儿的事
Next, we have to talk about my daughter.
她什么事?
What about her?
当然是想她回来
I want her back, of course.
好 我想我妻子回来
Yeah, well, I want my wife back.
那就没什么问题了
Then there should be no problem.
简现在在哪?
Where's Jane now?
在来这的路上 大约5分钟后到达
She's on her way here. She should be here in about 5 minutes.
很好 她到了以后 挑选你信得过的人看管她
Good. When she gets there, pick the men to guard her.
要确保他们会服从你的命令
Make sure they will follow your orders without question.
如果我女儿有任何闪失 你妻子就要死
If any harm comes to my daughter, your wife dies.
如果接到我的命令后 简还没有被释放 你妻子也得死
If Jane is not released when I order it, your wife dies.
就这样 明白了?
That's all you need to know. Are we clear?
托尼 你在吗?
Tony, are you in there?
托尼 总统先生的电话
Tony, President Palmer is on the line for you.
我会做到我的事 你也别食言
I will do my part. You do yours.
这样才对嘛
That's the spirit.
托尼 在吗?
Tony, are you there?
亚当 我在
Adam, I am here.
你还好吗?
Are you ok?
-没事 接过来  -好 稍等
-Yeah, I am fine. Put the President through.  -Ok, hang on.
我是托尼·阿尔梅达
This is Tony Almeida.
请稍等片刻
Please hold for the President.
阿尔梅达先生
Mr. Almeida.
我刚听说你们没抓到斯蒂芬 桑德斯 情况属实?
I just heard you lost Stephen Saunders. Is that true?
很不幸 总统阁下 是的
Yes, sir. Unfortunately, it is.
反恐局不是已经锁定他的藏匿地点了吗 怎么回事?
I thought CTU was certain of his location. What happened?
我们正在调查 总统先生
We are looking into it now, sir.
桑德斯知不知道他女儿在我们手上?
Does Saunders know we are holding his daughter?
他知道 总统先生
Yes, sir, he does.
很显然 他很在乎自己女儿
And she's obviously very important to him.
简 桑德斯在你那边吗?
Is Jane Saunders with you now?
还没有 正在路上
No. She's on her way here right now, sir.
阿尔梅达先生 我想不用我提醒你们必须看好她吧
Mr. Almeida, I don't have to remind you how much security we are going to need around her today.
她是阻止斯蒂芬 桑德斯继续要挟政府的唯一希望了
She is the only thing that is standing between us and Stephen Saunders controlling the government.
是 总统先生
Yes, Mr. President.
-我们知道该怎么做  -很好
-We're aware of that.  -Good
随时向我汇报
Keep me posted.
是 总统先生
Yes, sir.
谢谢 总统先生
Thank you, sir.
参议员 基勒参议员 你认为这会对你的竞选造成不利影响吗?
Senator, Senator Keeler, do you feel this is going to do serious damage to your campaign?
我相信绝对不会
Oh, absolutely not.
我以往在劳资问题上提案能说明问题 请记住我曾经投票反对北美自由贸易区
My record on labor speaks for itself Remeber I voted againt NAFTA.
而且我支持对国内制造业采取激励性税收政策
And I favor tax incentives for domestic manufacturing.
你失去的那些支持又怎么说呢?
And what about the other endorsements you lost?
谁转而不支持他了?
Who did he lose?
美国劳动联合会 美国产业工人联合会和一些退伍军人的组织
AFL CIO and a couple of veteran groups.
为什么?
Why?
很显然 他紧咬住您退出辩论的事不放引起了他们的反感
Apparently, they are not pleased with his negative spin on your withdrawal from the debate.
现在升级到红色警戒说明擅长玩弄政治的人不是您 而是他
Now that the threat level has been raised to red, people realize you aren't the one playing politics. He is.
现在可没时间考虑选举的事
We can't waste time thinking about the election right now.
现在最重要的事就是阻止斯蒂芬 桑德斯
The only thing that matters is stopping Stephen Saunders.
跟我来一下 失陪了 杰瑞
Would you come with me, please. Excuse us, Jerry.
不 亚当 他在那屋子里 我们发现了他用过的房间 我只想知道他是怎么逃出去的
No, Adam, he was in the building. We found the room he was using. I just want to know how he got out.
我们正在追查 蔡斯 一有结果就通知你
We are working on it, Chase. I will call you if we get something.
好
Good.
他怎么说?
What did he say?
我真不明白 杰克
I don't understand this, Jack.
我们锁定桑德斯的位置 他却凭空消失了
We pinpointed Saunders' location. He disappears into the air.
现在局里又说是卫星出了问题
Now CTU says they are having problems with the satellite.
我会查清楚的 贝克 我是杰克
We are looking into it.Baker, this is Jack.
两组巡逻 两组待命 收到了吗?
I want 2 teams on patrol, 2 more on standby. Copy?
我们怎么办?
What about us?
我们回局里 桑德斯打电话来的时候我得在他女儿边上
We will go over to CTU. I want to be with Saunders' daughter when he calls us back.
好
All right.
桑德斯是怎么逃脱的? 每个出口我们都有人把守
How did Saunders get past us? We had every exit covered.
他能侵入我们的跟踪系统?
Did he have access to our tracking systems?
反恐局 奥布莱恩
CTU, O'Brian.
克萝伊 我是杰克 你在忙什么?
Chloe, it's Jack. What are you working on?
我正试着寻找桑德斯的线索
We are all trying to pick up a thread on Saunders.
我在分析他打给你的最后一个电话 看看有没有载波信号
I am analyzing his last phone call to you to see if there's any tell on the carrier.
他有没有可能根本不在那?
Is it possible that he wasn't even in the building?
而只是从那转接电话?
That he was just routing his calls through there?
不可能 他在之间那间屋子已经转接过了
No. He did that earlier at the apartment.
既然我已经破解了他的假信号 他再要转接我肯定会知道
Now that I have his counterfeit signature, he wouldn't be able to do it without our knowing it.
好 有线索立刻通知我
Ok. Get back to me as soon as you have got anything.
有些不对劲
Something is not right here.
-这里就是反恐局?  -是
-This is CTU?  -Yes.
金 你爸爸说他和蔡斯正赶回来
Kim, your father wants you to know that he and Chase are on their way back.
-抓到桑德斯了?  -没有
-With Saunders?  -No.
怎么会呢?
Why not?
他不在那屋子里 他们正在追查他的下落
He wasn't in the building They are still trying to locate him.
-他们没抓到我父亲?  -没有
-They haven't captured my father?  -No.
但他知道我在你们手上 对吗?
But he knows you have me, right?
没错 他知道
Yes, he does.
福雷斯特探员 我是托尼·阿尔梅达
Agent Forrester, Tony Almeida.
我们打算把桑德斯小姐扣押在拘留室
We are going to be putting Miss Saunders in the holding room.
原来不是说关在无菌室吗?
I was told you were setting up a white room for her.
是 计划有变
Yeah. That's changed.
如果你想送她到后面 警卫会在那里接管
If you walk her to the back, Security will take her from there.
你会没事的?
You will be fine, ok?
你还好吗?
How are you doing?
真不敢相信竟然让桑德斯跑了
I can't believe that Saunders escaped.
我是说 这怎么可能呢? 他不是被包围了吗
I mean, how could this happen? I thought that he was surrounded.
就这么发生了 听着 瑞伊·普拉切基有话要问你
It happened. Look, Rae Plachecki's coming here to talk to you.
你可能要回答一些有关图书馆枪击案的问题
You're going to have to answer some questions about the shooting at the library.
好吧 我听说米歇尔的事了
Ok, look, I heard the news about Michelle.
-什么事?  -她没被感染
-What news?  -That she isn't infected.
哦 是的
Oh, yeah.
很高兴她没事 真是太好了
I am really glad that she's ok. That's great.
是的 谢谢
Yeah, thanks.
没办法能肯定
There is no way to be exactly sure.
有些人五六个小时也没出现症状
Some people don't show symptoms for 5 or 6 hours.
-亚当  -他有没有告诉你别的选择?
-Adam.  -Didn't they talk to you about your options?
他们说可以给我一种药...
They said they could give me a pill...
亚当 我有事和要你谈谈
Adam, I need to talk to you now.
萨拉 等等我正和我姐姐通话
Sarah, hold on. I am talking to my sister right now.
感染病毒那个?
The one who got infected with the virus?
明知故问 克萝伊
I am not even going to answer that, Chloe.
对不起 我等你打完
I am sorry. I'll just wait here until you are done.
-克萝伊  -亚当 抱歉 真的有要紧事
-Chloe.  -Adam, I am sorry, this is really important.
我需要马上和你谈
I just need you to finish up as quickly as you can.
萨拉 我一有空就打给你 好吗?
Sarah, I am going to have to call you back as soon as I can, ok?
好
Ok.
-我爱你  -我也爱你
-I love you.  -I love you.
-什么事?  -我和卫星部门核对过了
-What?  -I checked with satellite navigation.
他们说这儿有些图像不见了 他们肯定已经发给我们了
They said there are missing frames and they are certain it's on our end.
备份的图像资料呢?
What about the back up on the FGA volume?
也没了 还有 少了20秒的图像
Gone. Not only that, they cover about 20 seconds.
如果桑德斯确实在那屋子 一定就是那段时间逃跑的
So if Saunders did escape the building it would be the exact interval.
正巧那段时间发生故障?
So there was a glitch at exactly the wrong moment?
对 你觉得可能吗?
Yeah. What are the chances of that?
不对劲
Not good.
我认为桑德斯入侵了我们的系统
So I am thinking Saunders has access to our system.
你告诉托尼了吗?
Did you tell Tony yet?
还没 我想多收集些证据
No. I want more information before I go to him.
我检查了现场行动人员 他们的系统都没问题
But I checked with Field Ops, and all their systems are accounted for.
你去查一下通讯部门
I need you to do the same in Comm.
你真的认为反恐局有人给桑德斯做内应?
Do you really think there's someone inside CTU working for Saunders?
只有这个解释了
That's the only thing that makes sense right now.
如果你能尽快查出来 你就可以打电话给你姐姐了
So if you could just do that, and then you could call your sister back.
-嘿 皮特 我要和她谈一会  -自便
-Hey, Pete, I need few minutes.  -Sure thing
你怎么样?
How you doing?
我做错了什么事 为什么这么对待我?
Why am I being treated like I have done something wrong?
我向你道歉
I apologize for that.
我们是为了你的安全着想
We are just trying to keep you safe.
在这里我才会不安全呢
This is the one place I am not safe.
我一直在想
I have been thinking about it.
你们要利用我抓我父亲 所以一定会威胁要杀了我或者伤害我
You need me to get to my father, so threatening to kill me or harm me is the only tool you have to use against him.
告诉我 我说错了
Tell me I am wrong.
你说的没错
You are right.
我们要让你父亲相信我们为了抓到他会不择手段
We need your father to believe we will do anything to get him.
但我们不会伤害你
But we are not going to hurt you.
我保证
I give you my word.
-你的保证?  -没错 我的保证
-Your word?  -Yeah, my word.
我是这里的负责人 我会亲自保护你
I run this office and I will personally protect you.
那金的父亲呢? 他们告诉我他正赶过来
What about Kim's father? They told her that he is on his way back here.
-他怎么了?  -他恐吓我
-What about him?  -He scares me.
我感觉他会伤害我
I got the feeling he's willing to hurt me.
没人会伤害你
Nobody's going to hurt you.
知道吗?
All right?
希望你说的是真的
I wish I could believe you.
阿尔梅达
Almeida.
-简被送到了吗?  -到了
-Has Jane arrived?  -Yeah.
-她在哪?  -就在我旁边
-Where is she?  -She is here.
-让她听电话  -不行
-Put her on.  -No.
我要先和我妻子通话
You have my wife, I want to talk to her first.
你没资格跟我提要求
You don't give me orders.
你错了
You are wrong.
你女儿在我手里 我说了算
I have your daughter which means I am in charge.
如果你敢碰我的妻子 我就割断简的喉咙
Now if you so much as touch my wife, I will slit Jane's throat.
等等
Hold on.
抱歉让你受苦了
Sorry for your discomfort.
希望这只是暂时的 解开手铐
Hopefully it's temporary. Uncuff her.
我让你和你丈夫通话
I am going to let you speak to your husband.
告诉他你没事 平安无事
Tell him that you are ok and you are being treated well.
仅此而已 明白吗?
Nothing else. Understood?
托尼 是我
Tony, it's me.
米歇尔
Michelle.
他们不让我多说
They won't let me say much.
你还好吗?
Are you all right?
很好 没受虐待
I am fine. I am being treated well.
不要答应他们 不要...
Don't let them do this, don't let...
-够了  -米歇尔
-None of that.  -Michelle.
让我和我女儿通话 阿尔梅达先生
Let me speak with my daughter, Mr. Almeida.
你父亲要和你通话
It's your father. He wants to talk to you.
-爸爸?  -简 是我
-Dad?  -Yes, Jane. It's me.
他们说你做了可怕的事
They are saying horrible things about you.
别相信他们 这是他们的惯用的伎俩
That's what they do. Don't believe any of it.
在酒店的投放病毒害死很多人的不是你吧
The virus in the hotel, it's killing all of those people, you didn't do that.
告诉我这和你无关
Please tell me that you didn't do that.
听着 简
Listen to me, Jane.
美国政府扭曲事实 残害生命
The US government distorts the truth and destroys lives.
别听他们的 那都是假话
Don't listen to any of it. It's all lies.
那你没做过?
Then you didn't do it?
我所做的事情都有正当理由 这你是知道的
I'd never do something without good cause. You know that.
好了
That's all.
开始吧
Let's do these.
你要多久才能把她救出来?
What will it take for you to get her out of the building?
我要伪造一些通行证件 大概要30到40分钟
I have to fabricate some clearances. It's going to take me about 30 to 40 minutes.
你们一出反恐局就打电话给我
Contact me as soon as you are clear of CTU.
记下这号码
Take down this number.
你猜对了 托尼那个用户组的某人删除了卫星监控图像
You were right. Someone from Tony's group purged the frames from the surveillance feed.
知道是谁吗?
Do you know who?
匿名登陆的 可能是这里也可能是分局
It was a no name login. It could have been from here or Division.
我要去告诉托尼让他关闭系统
I'd better tell Tony so he can lock down the system.
好
Ok.
反恐局 奥布莱恩
CTU, O'Brian.
我是卫生局的桑尼 马切尔
This is Sunny Macer from Health Services.
桑尼 需要帮忙吗?
Sunny, what can I do for you?
最近半小时有没有米歇尔·德斯勒的消息?
Have you heard from Michelle Dessler in the last half hour?
没有 她不是送你那观察了吗
No, she was sent to your office for observation.
对 这正是我打电话来的原因
Well, that's actually why I am calling.
我收到指令要把她送去郡医院 但她不在那 显然也不在我这
I got a message that she asked to be taken to County instead, but she's not at County and she's definitely not here.
我们联络不到她
We can't get ahold of her.
我查一下再联络你
I will check on it and get back to you.
好的 谢谢
All right, thanks.
-我是戴维斯  -戴维斯 给我接迈克·雷德蒙 他和米歇尔·德斯勒
Davis, get me Mike Redmond. He's with Michelle Dessler.
好的
All right.
他没有应答
He's not answering.
没有应答是什么意思?
What do you mean he's not answering?
他在执勤 他必须应答
He's active. He has to answer.
他没有应答
He's not answering.
好吧 找到他立即通知我
Ok, I heard you the first time.
你确定?
Are you sure about this?
是的 托尼 当然确定
Yes, Tony, of course I am sure.
你这个用户组有79个人 有人在卫星的上行链路上搞鬼
There's 79 users in your group, and one of them has been playing games with the uplink recording.
好吧
All right, well.
锁定所有系统
We are going to have to lock everything down then.
完全赞同
Well, obviously I agree.
现在就去吗?
You want me to do it now?
是
Yeah.
什么事?
What is it?
米歇尔可能出事了
Something weird is happening with Michelle.
什么意思?
What do you mean?
我们和她失去联络 雷德蒙d也不复机
No one can find her, and Redmond's not answering his pages.
那是因为我撤出了NHS的命令
That's because I overrode NHS's order.
我不想让他们知道
I didn't want them to know about it.
我送米歇尔到我们的一个分局隔离 她在那还能继续工作
I am putting Michelle in quarantine in one of our substations so she can still do some work.
我需要人手
I need every warm body I can get.
我怎么和马切尔说?
What am I going to tell Macer?
我来和她说
I will call her.
有别的事要你做
There's something else I want you to do.
什么事?
What is it?
我给你几分钟前我和桑德斯的通话记录
I am sending you the record of a phone call between Saunders and myself from a few minutes ago.
你和他通过话?
You just spoke to him?
是的 我要你去掉载波信号 看是否能找到他
Yeah. I want you to strip away the carrier signal, see if you can use it to find him.
为什么不试试声音追踪?
What about the voice track?
不行 他做了干扰 没用的
No, he scrambled it. It's useless.
好吧
Fine.
克萝伊.
Chloe
去技术一室 别让人看见
Do it in tech one, away from everybody.
我不希望亚当知道这件事
I didn't want Adam to know about it.
为什么?
Why not?
嗯 事实上这是他的工作
Well, technically it's his job.
但你更出色
But you are better at it.
为什么这么说?
Why did you just say that?
因为这是事实
Because it's true.
见鬼 马克 你向我保证现在攻击帕默尔是正确的选择
Damn it, Mark, you assured me that going on the offensive against Palmer was the right thing to do.
现在尝到后果了
Now it's backfiring.
得了吧 约翰 这不公平
Come on, John. That's not fair.
你一指控他的女朋友 帕默尔就退出了辩论
Palmer walks out of the debate moments after you brought up the charge against his girlfriend.
每个人都会认为国家安全不过是个借口
Everyone assumed that he whole national security excuse was just a cover.
但显这并不是借口
Well, apparently it wasn't.
现在已升至红色警戒 机场也关闭了
The alert level is at red and the airports are shut down.
-我知道  -好吧
-I know.  -All right.
帕默尔还没有告诉公众关于威胁的细节
Palmer still hasn't told the public any of the details about this threat.
打给国防部的亚历克斯 看有什么头绪
Call Alex in the Pentagon see what you can find out about it.
根据结果 说不定我得抢先公开向他道歉
Depending on what it turns out to be, I may need to be proactive and issue an apology.
喂
Yeah.
什么事?
What's this about?
好 你等等 是雪莉 帕默尔
All right, hold on.It's Sherry Palmer.
她5分钟后要来拜访你
She wants to come here in 5 minutes.
-来干嘛?  -她没说
-Why?  -She wouldn't say.
只说她有极具价值的建议 要和您当面谈
Except that it's a high value proposition, and she wants to present it face to face.
安排一下
Set it up.
好 参议员马上到
All right, the Senator will be here.
一定很有意思
This should be interesting.
我去下载一些资料
I will off load the systems in Field Ops.
我马上过去
I will be right up.
-亚当 托尼在哪?  -和简 桑德斯在一起
-Adam, where's Tony?  -He's with Jane Saunders.
金在配合枪击事件的调查 我在配合NHS
Kim's waiting to be debriefed on the shooting and I am working with NHS.
NHS? 你为什么不盯住桑德斯?
NHS? Why aren't you tracking Saunders?
我不知道
I don't know.
托尼让克萝伊负责
Tony put Chloe in charge of that.
-克萝伊在哪?  -技术一室
-Where's Chloe?  -Tech one.
她为什么不在这?
Why isn't she in Field Ops?
你还没和托尼谈过?
You haven't talked to Tony yet?
谈什么?
About what?
杰克 托尼那个用户组的某个人清除一段桑德斯的卫星监控图像
Jack, it looks like someone from Tony's group intentionally wiped out those SAT frames from the Saunders' surveillance.
-所以他才会跑掉  -什么?
-That's how he was able to evade us.  -What?
亚当 NHS需要你的合作否则就要扩大隔离区域了
Adam, NHS wants those coordinates now, or they are going to have to widen the quarantine zone.
好的 我就知道这些 杰克
Ok. That's all I know, Jack.
-我回头在来查这事  -好吧
-I got to get back on this.  -Ok, fine.
也许我们几分钟就要将你转移
We may be moving you in a few minutes.
-去哪?  -分局
-Where?  -To Division.
什么地方?
What's that?
-喂  -托尼 我是杰克 我要和你谈谈
-Yeah.  -Tony, it's Jack.I need to speak with you.
观察室外见
Meet me outside the observation room.
好 我马上回来
Yeah, all right.I will be right back.
杰克 出什么事了?
Jack,What the hell's going on?
亚当刚告诉我 这有桑德斯的内奸
Adam just told me that you think you have got someone on the inside working with Saunders.
对 但还没能证实 克萝伊正在处理
Well, it hasn't been confirmed yet. Chloe's working on it.
她在干什么?
What's she doing?
她在检查日志信息 看看有没有什么异常
She's taking a look at status logs, to see if she can find anything out of the ordinary.
托尼 如果这是真的 我们就得打电话给分局 立刻派特别行动组来
Tony, if this is true, we have got to call Division, get Spec Ops down here immediately.
我也想过
I thought about that.
但我不想打草惊蛇
But I don't want to raise any red flags.
如果这有桑德斯的内奸 我不想惊动他们
If someone in our group is working with Saunders, I don't want them to know that we are onto them.
好吧 我们一起解决
Ok, fine.You and I will work this up together.
但我要让分局派人来接走简继续审问
But I want division to come pick up Jane so they can continue questioning her.
好主意
Good idea.
我去打给布拉德 哈蒙德 我们在技术一室碰头 我要好好问一问克萝伊
I will call Brad Hammond, I will meet you in tech one, we'll go through everything with Chloe.
不 等等 杰克
No, wait, Jack.
我每隔三十分钟都要向哈蒙德汇报
Look, I have a 30 minute status call scheduled with Hammond, anyway.
我来告诉他 你到上面指挥中心吧?
Why don't you let me tell him and you can go up to Field Ops?
好
Ok, fine.
亚当 托尼是不是每隔三十分钟都要向布拉德 哈蒙德汇报?
Adam.Is Tony set up for 30 minute status calls with Brad Hammond?
-我这里没有记录  -谢谢
-If he is, it's not in the books.  -Thanks.
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
-约翰 你好  -雪莉
-John, hello.  -Sherry.
很高兴见到你 我想你还不认识马克·卡纳 我的竞选经理
How nice to see you. I don't believe you know Mark Kaner, my campaign manager.
对 还没有 久仰大名 幸会
No, I don't. Only by reputation.Pleased to meet you.
你好
How do you do?
什么风把你吹来了?
So what brings you here?
嗯 实际上是私事 约翰
Well, actually, it's a private mater, John.
你先出去 马克
Let us have a minute, Mark
没问题
No problem.
请
Please.
我早上听说你失去了一些支持
I heard about the endorsements you lost this morning.
小小波动
Daily fluctuation. It doesn't mean a thing.
没什么大不了的
Doesn't mean a thing.
真是乐观啊 约翰
That's pretty optimistic, John.
不 你的竞选要失败了
No, your campaign is imploding.
等新闻界有机会分析一下你昨晚犯的错误
By the time the press has a chance to analyze all the mistakes you made last night.
你就会像个绝望的候选人 只剩下最后一口气了
You will look like a desperate candidate gasping his last breath.
听着 雪莉 如果你是来羞辱我的 我可没时间陪你
Look, Sherry, if you just came here to insult me, I am rather busy.
不 不 不 约翰
No, no, no, John.
正好相仿 放轻松
On the contrary. Relax.
我来是保证你在十一月的大选中获胜
I, I came here because I can guarantee you a win in November.
约翰 下面我要告诉你的事 如果你拿来对付我 我死都不会承认
John, what I am about to tell you, I will deny to my grave if you try to hold it against me.
明白了吗?
So that's clear, right?
约翰 你听明白了 是吗?
John, we are clear on that, right?
很好
Good.
大卫·帕默尔是谋杀案的同谋
David Palmer is an accessory to murder.
-什么谋杀案?  -艾伦·米利肯
-Who's murder?  -Alan Milliken.
艾伦·米利肯死于心脏病
Alan Milliken died of a heart attack.
是的 但这本可以避免
Yes, he did, but he didn't have to.
他的硝化甘油就在触手可及的地方
His nitroglycerin was just an arm's length away.
但他够不到 因为有人阻止了他
But he couldn't get to it because someone kept it from him.
你怎么知道?
Now how could you possibly know that?
因为那个人就是我
Because that someone was me.
雪莉 你最好现在就离开
Sherry, I think you had better leave right now.
真的?
Really?
你想结束自己的政治生涯吗?
So you can watch your entire career leave with me?
如果你说的是实话 我可不想和你扯上什么关系
If what you are saying is true, I don't want to have anything to do with you.
哦 拜托 算了吧 约翰
Oh, come on, spare me, John.
如果你没做过什么见不得人的事 也不会走到这一步了
You haven't gotten this far without getting a little dirt under your fingernails.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you are talking about.
你当然不知道
No. Of course not.
为了能继续谈下去 我仔细说一下
But for the sake of conversation, just allow me to paint you a picture.
我...
I...
拜托 不会很久的
Please, it won't take but a moment.
满足我的这小小的要求吧
Just indulge me.
很好
Very well.
大卫昨天向警察总长说谎 为我提供不在场证据
David lied to the Chief of Police last night in order to provide an alibi for me.
而且我可以证明他在说谎
And I can prove that he lied.
不 你想想
No, you think about that.
美国总统为了掩盖谋杀案而说谎的证据
Proof that the President of the United States lied to cover a murder.
什么证据?
What kind of proof?
除了我的供词?
Besides my confession?
我有他要服用的那瓶药
I have the prescription bottle he was reaching for.
在我手上
I was holding it.
很安全
And I have it in a very safe place.
你是在指控你自己
You are talking about incriminating yourself.
你会坐牢的
You would go to prison.
是 我知道
Yes, I know that.
但大卫也会
But so would David.
大卫为了保住自己而向警察说谎
David lied to the police to save himself.
这很简单 约翰
It's quite simple, John.
你要做的就是告诉大卫 你掌握了这个证据
All you have to do is go to David and tell him that you have this evidence.
那个有我指纹的药瓶
This medicine bottle with my fingerprints on it.
我保证大卫会退出竞选
And I guarantee you David will drop out of the race.
他们党内会乱成一团 没有人可以阻止你11月的当选
The party will be thrown into turmoil and nobody, I mean nobody will be able to touch you come November.
你想要什么?
And for all of this?
给我在白宫找份差事做
You will put me on the White House staff.
职务不用太高 以免引来非议
Nothing so high that it will raise too many eyebrows.
你做这一切就为了在我的政府里做一个中层官员?
All of this for you to be a mid level staffer in my administration?
你我都知道还有其他的一些原因
You and I both know that it would be a little more than that.
你是说预计伤亡人数会上升
So you are saying the casualty estimates have been projected upward.
恐怕是的 总统先生
Yes sir, I am afraid so.
预计上升多少?
By a factor of how many?
如果病毒没有被完全控制流出酒店的话
Now that the virus is out of the hotel and not completely contained.
也许会上升五倍
It could be as high as times five.
好吧 谢谢 Dan 有情况随时报告
All right, thanks, Dan. Keep me posted.
是的 总统先生
Yes, sir.
什么事?
What's it?
我在基勒竞选办公室的一个线人刚打来电话
I just got off the phone with one of my sources over at Keeler's headquarters.
雪莉去那和基勒秘密会见
Sherry was there meeting privately with Keeler.
-什么时候?  -就在刚才
-When?  -Just now.
见基勒干什么?
Meeting Keeler about what?
他打探不到 大卫
He didn't know. David.
我以为你知道点什么
So I was hoping you'd have some idea.
我不知道她在干什么
I don't know what she's doing.
但我们现在管不了这么多了
But we can't worry about that now.
洛杉矶正有人死去
There are people dying here in Los Angeles.
是的 我可不喜欢 大卫
Yeah, well, I don't like it, David.
-让我派人处理下吧  -不用
-So let me put someone on this.  -No.
我让雪莉来处理这个问题 看最后会怎么样
I brought Sherry in to fix a problem, and look what happened.
随它去吧
Just let it be.
很快就会有消息的
We will hear soon enough.
什么情况?
What do you see?
他们在通过敞开式电话转接器追踪我们
They are trying to use the open phone switches to find us.
我打给他的那个电话已经关机了
The phone I called him with is shut off.
他们没办法锁定我们的位置 对吗?
They can't triangulate me, can they?
暂时不会
Not quickly.
但他们可以反复试验得到近似结果
But they can try a trial and error process and that could get them close.
这就是他们的方法?
And that's what they are doing?
应该是
Looks like it.
我们得阻止他们
Then we will have to stop them.
跟我来
Come with me.
你们的人正利用我上次的通话追踪我
Your office is using our last phone conversation to locate us.
他们是怎么做的?
How are they doing it?
我发誓要救回我女儿
I am committed to getting my daughter back.
你杀了我 就永远不可能了
You kill me and that'll never happen.
这可不是唯一的选择
That's not the only option.
你很迷人
You are an attractive woman.
我想你丈夫不会希望你被毁容
I am guessing your husband would prefer you returned without a disfigurement.
我什么都不会告诉你
I am not telling you anything.
我要和阿尔梅达谈谈
I have to talk to Almeida.
长话短说
Keep your conversation short.
-阿尔梅达  -让我描述一下
-Almeida.  -Let me paint you a picture.
一把尖刀正划过你妻子的脸 鲜血正往下滴
I have a sharp knife, the tip of which is drawing blood from your wife's face right now.
如果你不在30秒内停止追踪我 你就会再也认不出她了
If whatever you are doing to trace these phone calls doesn't stop in 30 seconds, she'll be unrecognizable.
奥布莱恩.
O'Brian
停止追踪
Shut down the trace.
停止? 我刚有点进展
Shut it down? I am just starting to get something.
快停止 克萝伊
Do it now, Chloe.
好吧 至少让我看看能不能分离出音频
Fine. Let me at least see if I can unscramble the audio.
不 你先停几分钟
No, I need you to hold off for a few minutes.
没道理啊 托尼
This doesn't make sense, Tony.
你不是要我追踪桑德斯吗
I thought you wanted me to find Saunders.
是没错 我稍后再和你解释
I do. I will explain it to you later.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
我正在跟进桑德斯的一条线索
I am trying to pick up a thread on Saunders.
我的用户组里有内奸 隔离区像雨后春笋一样不停增加
Somebody in my own group may be working against us, I have quarantine zones springing up all over the place.
我已经精疲力尽了 杰克
I am treading water here, Jack.
为什么对我说谎?
Why are you lying to me?
说谎? 你在说什么?
Lying? What are you talking about?
我刚和哈蒙德通过话
I just got off the phone with Hammond.
你们之间没有电话报告的程序
You didn't have a status call scheduled.
刚才我出丑了
I screwed up earlier.
我自己的人在我的系统里面伪造卫星图像
The SAT transmission on my system was forged by my own people.
我该在命令贝克撤出预定位置之前就发现的 但我没有
I should have noticed that it wasn't authentic before I ordered Baker off his post, I didn't.
但当我意识到错误的时候 已经太晚了 桑德斯已经跑了
By the time I realized my mistake, it was too late. Saunders was gone.
那丢失的图像怎么解释?
What about the missing frames?
一定是伪造卫星图像的人删除的
They must have been deleted by the same person who forged the SAT transmission.
听着 我知道这事不小 杰克 这次行动以后 我会辞职
Look, I know this is big, Jack, and I promise you I will offer my resignation when this day is over.
但现在我还有很多事要做
Right now we got too much going on for me to step down.
犯错是一回事
Making a mistake is one thing.
试图掩盖又是另一回事
Covering it up is another.
我不能让你在留下来了
I can't let you stay in place.
我现在要接管反恐局
I am taking over command of CTU now.
我只是犯了个错误 杰克
I made a mistake, Jack.
不 托尼
No, Tony.
你犯了两个错误
You made two.
好 我让亚当把所有资料传给你
Fine. I will make sure Adam sends over everything I have got to your group.
托尼 我缩小了可能名单范围
Tony, I narrowed down the list.
什么名单?
What list?
那些在卫星图像丢失时无法提供不在场证据的人员名单
The list of people on your team that can't account for their time when the SAT frames went missing.
哦 好的
Oh, yeah, right.
托尼 很有可能就是这个名单上的某个人从反恐局内部帮助桑德斯
Tony, it's very likely that someone on this list is working from within CTU to help Saunders.
嗯 亚当 我现在不负责反恐局了
Look, Adam, I am not in charge of CTU anymore.
你说什么?
What are you talking about?
杰克和我决定还是由他来接管
Jack and I have decided it'd be best if he took over.
把名单送去给哈蒙德 好吗?
Why don't you send that list over to Hammond, all right?
喂
Yes.
我遇到麻烦了
I got a problem.
什么麻烦?
What problem?
杰克·鲍尔刚刚解除了我的指挥权
Jack Bauer just relieved me of my command.
他为什么这么做?
Why did he do that?
他发现我删除了那些卫星图像
He found out I'd deleted those satellite frames.
他知道我们的暗中联络吗?
Does he know about our communication?
不 还没有 他以为我在掩盖我犯的错误
No, not yet. He thinks I am just covering my mistake.
不过他很快会发现
But he's gonna find out soon.
我建议你在他发现之前 带我女儿离开
Then I suggest you get my daughter out of there before he does.
听着 我现在不可能做到了
Look, I might not be able to do this.
我在反恐局已经没有权限了
I no longer have any authority at CTU.
你不需要什么所谓的权限 托尼
You don't' need authority, Tony.
不管什么原因 只要你不把简交给我
You just need to know that if you don't deliver Jane for whatever reason,
你老婆就会像瑞恩·查佩尔一样死去
your wife will die just like Ryan Chappelle died.
就像钱德勒 广场酒店的人一样死去
Just like the people at the Chandler Plaza Hotel died.
我现在就想办法救她 但如果不行
I am gonna try to get her out, but if I can't.
如果你做不到 米歇尔就死定了
If you can't, Michelle dies.
在把简安全救出来之前别打电话给我
Don't call me again until you have Jane safely away.
-爸爸  -金 我要你帮忙
-Dad.  -Kim, I need you to help me with something.
你和托尼说清楚了
You are gonna have to clear it with Tony.
他让我向瑞伊·普拉切基报告简 桑德斯的事
He wants me to debrief with Rae Plachecki about what's going on with Jane Saunders.
托尼已经引咎辞职了
Tony just stepped down.
我现在暂时接管反恐局
I am acting director of CTU until further notice.
托尼引咎辞职是什么意思 ?
What do you mean Tony stepped down?
托尼向我隐瞒事实
Tony's hiding something from me.
我要你帮我查出是什么
I need you to help me find out what it is.
为什么找我?
Why me?
因为现在我没有任何人可以信任
Because right now I don't know who to trust.
我要你监视反恐局的每个节点
I need you to maintain a surveillance on every station here at CTU.
监视任何人的出入 监听2级权限以上的通讯
Anyone who checks in or out, and I also want you to track communications that flag higher than a code 2.
去哪做?
Where do you want me to do that?
指挥中心 来吧
Field Ops. Come on.
谢谢
Thanks.
阿尔梅达.
Almeida
好消息 托尼
Good news, Tony.
什么?
What is it?
我找到从你和桑德斯的通话录音中剥离出音频的办法了
I found a way to pull the voice track on the phone call you had with Saunders.
有没有听过?
Have you listened to it yet?
没 还在运算中
No. The algorithm is still running.
一旦完成 我就可以分析背景音了
But once that's complete, I will be able to do an analysis on the ambient sound and room tone.
干得好
All right, good work.
亚当 把你的资料传到金的电脑
Adam, I want you to send your volumes up to Kim's computer.
我要让她帮我查点东西
I have her checking something for me.
好
Ok.
克萝伊还在技术一室?
Is Chloe still in Tech One?
好像是
As far as I know, she is.
让她到我办公室来 我有事和她谈
Have her come up to my office, I need to speak with her.
好的 我会的 杰克
Ok, I will, Jack.
考夫曼.
Kaufman
亚当 我要和克萝伊通话
Yeah, Adam, I am on the line with Chloe.
我要四号练习曲的密码
We need the password to Etudes 4.
是 BCF19.
BCF19
好 谢谢
All right, thanks.
哦 托尼 杰克让克萝伊去他办公室
Yeah, Oh, Tony, Jack needs to see Chloe in his office right away.
好 我会通知她
All right, I will tell her.
谢谢
Thank you.
她在哪?
Where is she?
在我旁边
She is here.
让她听电话
Put her on.
不行
No.
你抓了我妻子 我要先和她说话
You have my wife, I want to talk to her first.
你抓了我妻子?
You have my wife?
喂? 喂?
Hello? Hello?
该死
Damn it.
救命 来人啊 救命 我被锁住了
Help, somebody help, I am locked in.
技术一室 我被锁住了
Tech one, I am locked in.
打断一下
Just hold on for a second.
大家注意了
Everybody, can I have your attention?
打断一下 请注意
Just stop working for a second. I need your attention.
从现在开始 由我暂管反恐局
From this point forward, I am taking command of CTU.
包括指挥中心和所有通联
That includes Field Ops and all communications.
托尼·阿尔梅达刚刚辞职
Tony Almeida has stepped down.
他已不再负责任何事务
He is no longer in charge.
我要送简 桑德斯去分局
I am taking Jane Saunders to Division.
这是移交手续
Here's the order.
我没时间细说了 现在我们的首要任务就是找到斯蒂芬 桑德斯
I don't have time to go into details, because right now we have to focus on finding Stephen Saunders.
拜托 皮特 这就是命令
Come on, Pete, this is the order right here.
如果你不相信 可以打去分局核实
You don't believe me, call Division talk to them yourself.
除非是直接和NHS合作划定隔离区的人 其他人都转到这个重点上来
So unless you are working directly with NHS in defining the quarantine zones, I need you to get involved.
去找你们的上级 他们会分配给你们任务
Check with your superiors, they will hand out your assignments.
我们必须马上找到这个家伙
We need to find this guy. Now.
我们马上离开
We are leaving right now.
好
Ok.
这边走
We are going out this way.
蔡斯 克萝伊已经有十五分钟没有更新表格了
Chase, Chloe hasn't refreshed her current tables in over 15 minutes.
她不在主系统上工作吗?
I thought she was working on the main system.
是的
Yeah, she was.
真奇怪
That's weird.
她从不会忘记
She never forgets to do that.
什么事?
What's going on?
你见过克萝伊吗?
Have you seen Chloe?
是的 她在技术一室
Yeah, she's over in Tech One.
警卫都去哪了?
Where are all the guards?
我们不需要警卫
We don't need those guards anymore.
为什么? 我还以为你们担心我父亲派人来救我
Why not? I thought you were worried about my father sending men in to get me.
这条街已经被我们监控 别担心
We have agents on the streets, don't worry about it.
金 为什么技术一室没有回应?
Kim, why can't I get a feed on Tech One?
等等
Hang on.
有人锁住了那
Someone blocked it.
有人入侵 取消那个密码
We have a hostile inside. Override the access code now.
警卫 扣留克萝伊·奥布莱恩
Perimeter security, I need a 20 on Chloe O'Brian.
首先派人彻底搜查这里
And a priority one sweep of the entire building.
守住后门
Cover the back entrance.
杰克.
Jack
克萝伊 离开电脑
Chloe, step away from the computer. Now.
托尼把我锁在这
Tony locked me in here.
桑德斯抓了米歇尔 用来交换他女儿
Saunders has Michelle, he's using her as leverage to get his daughter out.
别动
Don't move.
警卫 我是杰克·鲍尔
Security, this is Jack Bauer.
截住托尼·阿尔梅达
I need a 20 on Tony Almeida.
重复 截住托尼·阿尔梅达
I repeat, I need a 20 on Tony Almeida.
不行 杰克
Negative, Jack.
所有监控图像都找不到他
He's not on any of the monitors.
他什么时候把你锁在这的?
When did he lock you in here?
两分钟前
About 2 minutes ago.
让警卫封锁整幢大楼
Have security lock down the entire building.
亚当 让附近所有卫星监视我们
Adam, I want every SAT within range trained on us.
我要监控这栋大楼的所有出入
I want to know everything that's exiting this building.
谁在看着简 桑德斯?
Who's watching Jane Saunders?
两个警卫都倒下了 她跑了
Both guards are down, she's gone.
托尼.
Tony
各出口注意 截住托尼·阿尔梅达
Exit security, I need a 20 on Tony Almeida.
我是阿尔梅达 我们出来了 她在我这
This is Almeida. We are out. I have got her.
卫星多久才会发现你?
How long until satellite finds you?
大约30分钟
About 30 minutes.
我会在20分钟后给你下一步指示
I will give you further instructions in 20 minutes.
在泰勒大街和瓦因大街的东北角
Be at the northeast corner of Taylor and Vine.
好
Yeah, right.
打电话给帕默尔总统 告诉他我要亲自和他谈谈
Call President Palmer, tell him I need to speak with him in person.